# **BAHADIR SAYGILI**



#### Address:

16/5 Kart St. Selçuklu District 06940 Sincan/ANKARA

#### Tel:

+090 (507) 744 0839

#### **Email:**

bhdrsaygili@gmail.com

#### Website:

www.bahadirsaygili.com

### Socials:



https://www.linkedin.com/in/bahadir-saygili/



https://github.com/bsaygili

### **Summary**

Having gained the notion of engineering, I shaped my career by using the industrial engineering education effectively in my professional life.

My interest in software has always been a dimension that excited me inside. I became a self-taught front-end developer. I will continue to learn. Since my interest in software makes me feel more excited, being a front-end developer has always taken a place in my mind. For this reason, I have been a self-educated front-end developer and I will continue to improve myself.

An ambitious, enthusiastic, and open-to-learn front-end developer who cares about all aspects of the user experience using React, javascript, HTML and CSS.

## **Key Skills**

- Project Management
- Effective Decision Maker
- Problem Solver
- Leadership
- Innovative

# **Experience**

- Fanus Media, Freelance Front-End Developer, December
  2021 continue.
  - Developing responsive websites and e-commerce sites of clients with React,
  - Designed website including graphical user interface design and coding,
  - Knowledge of Web standards and protocols like HTML, CSS, HTTP, JavaScript with ES6 and React.js
- Balçık Heting Elements Co., Serial Manufacturing Planning Specialist, September 2018 - March 2022.
  - Making daily production plans,
  - Staff management,
  - Solution to daily problems in production with an engineering approach
- Turkish Air Force, Military Interceptor Officer, August 2014 -July 2018.
  - Preparing Flight Plans
  - Controlling Military Air Traffic
  - Ohserving Air Field for hostile/foreign Air Traffic

### **Education**

- Vocational School of Justice, Anadolu University 2014 2018.
  - Theorotical and practical knowledge with regard to qualificiations required by the justice service.
  - Sufficient knowledge of the law.
- Industrial Engineering, Turkish National Defense University 2010 – 2014.
  - Visual Ergonomics, Aesthetic and minimalist web design, Heuristic Evaluation
  - Sports Complex Layout for the Olympic Games to be Held in Istanbul with the Shortest Path Approach (as a graduation thesis.)

## **Front-end Skills**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React
- Redux

- Bootstrap
- Styled-Components
- Metarial UI
- Git
- NPM
- Webpack

## Language

Turkish: NativeEnglish: Fluent